'use client'
import { useState } from "react";
import { PiShuffleAngularBold } from "react-icons/pi";
import Flashcard from "@/components/flashcard";

const data = [
  {
    id: 0,
    question: "What is a startup?",
    answer: "A startup is a young company founded by entrepreneurs to develop and bring a unique product or service to market."
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "What is the role of a founder?",
    answer: "A founder is an individual who initiates and establishes a startup, often taking on multiple roles such as setting the vision, securing funding, and building a team."
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "what is SpeechSynthesisUtterance in nextjs14?",
    answer: "SpeechSynthesisUtterance is a built-in web API provided by modern browsers to enable text-to-speech functionality"
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "What is a business plan?",
    answer: "A business plan is a document that outlines the goals, strategies, and financial projections of a startup. It serves as a roadmap for the company's operations and growth."
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "What is bootstrapping?",
    answer: "Bootstrapping is a method of self-funding a startup's growth using personal savings, revenue generated by the business, or minimal external funding."
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "What is scalability in startups?",
    answer: "Scalability refers to a startup's ability to handle increased demand or growth without significant disruptions or loss in performance."
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "What is the role of venture capital in startups?",
    answer: "It helps startups accelerate growth, expand operations, and bring products to market."
  },

  {
    id: 7,
    question: "What is a business plan?",
    answer: "A business plan is a document that outlines the goals, strategies, and financial projections of a startup. It serves as a roadmap for the company's operations and growth."
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "What is bootstrapping?",
    answer: "Bootstrapping is a method of self-funding a startup's growth using personal savings, revenue generated by the business, or minimal external funding."
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "What is the role of a founder?",
    answer: "A founder is an individual who initiates and establishes a startup, often taking on multiple roles such as setting the vision, securing funding, and building a team."
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "What is the role of venture capital in startups?",
    answer: "It helps startups accelerate growth, expand operations, and bring products to market."
  },
]

export default function Home(props: any) {
  const [isLoadMore, setisLoadMore] = useState(false)
  const [shuffledData, setShuffledData] = useState(data)
  const handleLoadMore = () => {
    setisLoadMore(!isLoadMore)
  }
  const handleShuffle = (data: any) => {
    setShuffledData([...data].sort(() => Math.random() - 0.5))
  }

  return (
    <main>
      <div className="flex flex-col border p-[5%]">
        <div className="flex justify-between">
          <div className="">From articles...</div>
          <PiShuffleAngularBold size={18} onClick={(): void => handleShuffle(data)} className="cursor-pointer" />
        </div>

        <div className="grid grid-cols-1 sm:grid-cols-2 lg:grid-cols-3 2xl:grid-cols-4 justify-around gap-10 items-center">
          {
            shuffledData.map((item: any, index: number) => {
              return <>
                {
                  (isLoadMore ? item : index < 6) && <Flashcard key={item.id} question={item.question} answer={item.answer} />
                }
              </>
            })
          }
        </div>
        <div onClick={handleLoadMore} className={`text-center pt-4 cursor-pointer opacity-80 ${isLoadMore ? 'hidden' : ''}`}>Load more...</div>
        <div onClick={handleLoadMore} className={`text-center pt-4 cursor-pointer opacity-80 ${isLoadMore ? '' : 'hidden'}`}>Show less...</div>
      </div>
    </main >
  );
}
